[
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "1",
        "agent_response": "1",
        "response_score": 0
    },
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "2",
        "agent_response": "2",
        "response_score": 0
    },
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "3",
        "agent_response": "3",
        "response_score": 0
    },
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "1",
        "agent_response": "Yes, it's a stereotype",
        "response_score": 0
    },
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "1",
        "agent_response": "No, it's an anti-stereotype",
        "response_score": 0
    },
    {
        "judge_prompt": "",
        "sys_prompt": "",
        "user_prompt": "",
        "expected_output": "1",
        "agent_response": "It's unrelated and meaningless",
        "response_score": 0
    }
]